Send to Amazon or STA is the shipment creation workflow for fulfillment by Amazon or FBA.
This streamlined workflow helps you ship your FBA products to Amazon fulfillment centers.
To locate the STA page, open the Seller Central main menu, hover over Inventory and click Shipments.
You'll arrive at the shipping queue page, which provides the list of shipments you're working on,
and those you've already sent to Amazon.
From here, click Send to Amazon in the top shipments menu.
Note that the top shipments menu is also available on each FBA page, such as FBA inventory and shipments.
The STA workflow has a total of five steps.
However, the number of steps you need to complete
depends on whether you're shipping boxes or pallets and your choice of carrier.
You can learn
about each step in the Send to Amazon workflow by searching for Send to Amazon in Seller Central.